Contact

Almaty, Kazakhstan +77073574219 (Mobile) levhav@yandex.com

www.linkedin.com/in/victortrapenok (LinkedIn) github.com/VictorTrapenok (Personal) viktor-t.com/ (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Amazon Relational Database Service (RDS) Computer Science Project Management

Languages

Russian (Native or Bilingual) English (Full Professional) Ukrainian (Elementary)

Publications

Unifie - More than kubernetes control panel

How I Reduced CI/CD infrastructure costs at Nanoheal

Creating a simple chat using CppComet

Conference with a report about CppComet project

Telegram bot integration testing

Victor Trapenok

Principal Engineer @ Nanoheal | SaaS Cloud Projects Development (Open to relocation)

Almaty, Kazakhstan

Summary

At Nanoheal, as Principal Engineer, my focus has been on multitenant SaaS cloud projects, harnessing Kubernetes and cloud infrastructure to streamline deployments and enhance product demonstrations. The solutions developed under my leadership have significantly reduced deployment times, saving countless hours for our team and clients.

The ability to deploy services rapidly for testing has not only accelerated development cycles but also fortified our product's reliability and scalability.

Strong skils DevOps + Full-stack + cloud engineering allows me to get better result from contributing to code and infrustructure in the same time.

Open to relocation to USA / Europe

Experience

Nanoheal

3 years 7 months

Principal Engineer

March 2022 - Present (2 years 8 months)

Orem, Utah, United States

Development of a multi-tenant SaaS cloud project that provide web interface for managing kubernetes and deployments.

It decreased deploying time, and now product-sales for product demonstration can deploy nanoheal software from our internal ui in one of the existed clusters in several minutes. It save a lot of working time for whole team.

Developers and QA team can deploy all services from specified development brunches for testing.

Team Lead

April 2021 - April 2022 (1 year 1 month)

Orem, Utah, United States

Development of a multi-tenant SaaS cloud project with the placement of Kubernetes clusters in several regions of the most popular cloud providers such as AWS, Google Cloud Platform, Azure.

I am using Kubernetes, NodeJS, TypeScript, Terraform, GitLab, ReactJS, CubeJS, Ansible, Jira.

I am working remotely.

Cube Dev

Senior Software Engineer

August 2020 - March 2021 (8 months)

Vladivostok, Primorye, Russia

Work with Cube.js and cube.dev as a Full-stack developer (NodeJS, ReactJS, SQL).

As a DevOps engineer, I worked with infrastructure to run Kubernetes clusters in Google Cloud and AWS.

Noveo Group

Full-stack Developer

October 2019 - August 2020 (11 months)

Paris, Île-de-France, France

React.JS, TypeScript and NodeJS development for a large SaaS project.

SANCOM

Full-stack Developer

December 2018 - October 2019 (11 months)

Vladivostok, Primorye, Russia

Development and support of internal projects of the company.

I developed a system for detecting answering machines in phone call records.

This system uses an audio fingerprint for search to answering machine in the recording. Able to detect autoresponders in any language.

It builds reports on the reason why unable to call to client.

It already used to optimize the work of a several big call centers.

Individual entrepreneur Full Stack Developer

February 2017 - November 2018 (1 year 10 months)

Vladivostok, Primorye, Russia

I also have freelancing experience. I often receive orders for the development of chat.

For example, I am engaged in chat support on the website of the Russian television channel OTR (https://otr-online.ru/online/)

In general, during the study of the English language, I translated many of my articles and documentation from Russian to English (here is all the documentation on this site written by me https://comet-server.com/wiki/doku.php/en this took several years as I did in non-working hours)

VST Consulting
Software Programmer
February 2015 - November 2018 (3 years 10 months)
Vladivostok, Primorye, Russia

Regarding the experience of using ansible, I, in my past work at VST consalting, were developing the frontend for the Polemarch project (https://polemarch.org), here are the comits https://github.com/vstconsulting/polemarch/commits?author=Levhav and https://github.com/vstconsulting/vstutils/commits?author=Levhav

During the period of work in VST consalting, I participated in a project to develop a proxy accepting requests for speech synthesis using the protocol MRCPv2 or MRCPv1 and transmitting these requests to the REST API and then our proxy receiving in response the synthesized file reproduced it and sent it back to MRCPv2 or MRCPv1 for this we wrote a C plugin for the UniMRCP server.

worldpage.ru
Website Developer
February 2012 - January 2015 (3 years)
Vladivostok, Primorye, Russia

Business social network site.

I have developed such sections of the site as: Vacancies and Resumes, Blog, Site Search, Chat

Education

Far Eastern Federal University (FEFU)

Specialist Degree (Software engineer), Computing systems complexes and networks · (2010 - 2015)

Primorsky Polytechnic College secondary vocational education (Software engineer), Computer Programming · (2006 - 2010)

Secondary comprehensive school No. 66

Basic General Education · (September 1997 - May 2006)